<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>networking on Austin Barnes</title>
    <link>https://www.cinderblock.tech/tags/networking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in networking on Austin Barnes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cinderblock.tech/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rancher behind Traefik - K3S</title>
      <link>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/rancher-traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/rancher-traefik/</guid>
      <description>Using Rancher and Traefik to provide certificates and a management platform to a K3S Cluster In this guide, we will be creating an environment consisting of Rancher, Traefik, MySQL, and a K3S cluster. By setting it up this way, we can automate certificate management through Cloudflare (For more details about Cloudflare certificates behind Traefik, refer to other posts, as this won&amp;rsquo;t be covered here.)
Prerequisites To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll need:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsec &amp; Traefik: Automating Security in Your Homelab</title>
      <link>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/crowdsec-traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/crowdsec-traefik/</guid>
      <description>Crowdsec &amp;amp; Traefik: Automating Security in Your Homelab Hello there! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to introduce you to Crowdsec, an open-source Security threat intelligence project that&amp;rsquo;s perfect for boosting security in your homelab.
Prerequisites Before we embark on our journey into a safer network, let&amp;rsquo;s check off these prerequisites:
Prior experience with networking and a good understanding of network protocols. Some exposure to Docker as we&amp;rsquo;ll be using Docker-Compose for the setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible Semaphore - Automating Updates</title>
      <link>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/ansible-semaphore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/ansible-semaphore/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce you to Semaphore, an open-source Ansible management project. With Semaphore, you can automate and keep track of all your Ansible tasks in your homelab. Check out my current Ansible Playbooks in this GitHub repository.
Prerequisites Before we dive into Semaphore, let&amp;rsquo;s ensure you meet the following prerequisites:
Some prior experience with Ansible and understanding of playbook formatting. Ideally, some Docker experience as we&amp;rsquo;ll be using Docker-Compose for the setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TackleBox - GitHub Mega Repo</title>
      <link>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/github-tacklebox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cinderblock.tech/blog/github-tacklebox/</guid>
      <description>Overview Welcome to the TackleBox, my repository that houses a diverse collection of projects and scripts.
Check out all the goodies in this repo on GitHub.
A Quick Peek Greetings, fellow tech enthusiasts! I thought it would be a great idea to showcase the mishmash of projects and scripts I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated in this repository of mine, aptly named the TackleBox. Within this repository, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a wide range of content, from network automation scripts using PowerShell and Ansible to infrastructure-as-code solutions with Packer and Terraform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
